Guide to the Outdoor Advertising Association of America (OAAA) Archives, 1885-2017 and undated RL.00963
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- VIDEO, FILM AND AUDIO RECORDINGS, 1956-2002 and undated
  - Preservation Masters
    - HCD-OAAA-PD4--OAI, Wonderful World of Signs RSMC-1424/1425. Format: CD (Box VF31)
    - HCD-OAAA-PD5--General Foods, Getting More Customers. Format: CD (Box VF31)
    - HCD-OAAA-PD6--When America's Front Door Opens. Format: CD (Box VF31)
    - HCD-OAAA-PD7--Outdoor--Vital Medium in Today's Grocery Field. Format: CD (Box VF31)
    - HCD-OAAA-PD8--Your Outdoor Neighbor, Bell/Automatic 30-50 versions. Format: CD (Box VF31)
    - HCD-OAAA-PD9--Your Outdoor Neighbor, revised. Format: CD (Box VF31)
    - Data disc - .wav files of all audio recordings reformatted by ClairAudia. Format: CD (Box VF31)
  - Use Copies
    - Ambassador Austad at WMET. Format: Cassette. TRT: 18:30 (Box VF32)
    - American Planning Association, Street Graphics and Sign Regulation; Daniel Mandelker and Andrew Bertucci, Side 3. Format: Cassette (Box VF32)
    - American Planning Association, Street Graphics and Sign Regulation; Daniel Mandelker and Andrew Bertucci, Sides 1-2. Format: Cassette (Box VF32)
    - Bob Kuperman--Chiat/Day, Scottsdale, AZ, 1988 May. Format: Cassette (Box VF32)
    - F&K: It Pays to Be Creative. Format: Cassette. TRT: 24:00 (Box VF32)
    - F&K: Media Insurance. Format: Cassette. TRT: 15:00 (Box VF32)
    - F&K: Outdoor Sells, 1972 July. Format: Cassette. TRT: 9:00 (Box VF32)
    - F&K: The Sleeping Giant. Format: Cassette (Box VF32)
    - Newsmakers, WTMJ-AM. Format: Cassette. TRT: 16:30 (Box VF32)
    - Outdoor America, Scottsdale, 1988. Format: Cassette (Box VF32)
    - Outdoor Goes to College. Format: Cassette. TRT: 24:00 (Box VF32)
    - Posters Old and New, Part 1, 1976. Format: Cassette. TRT: 13:00 (Box VF32)
    - Posters Old and New, Part 2, 1976. Format: Cassette. TRT: 14:07 (Box VF32)
    - Principal's Panel, Scottsdale AZ, 1988 May. Format: Cassette (Box VF32)
    - Reading of statement by Charles Olsen of Notre Dame,1971 Apr.1. Format: Cassette (Box VF32)
    - Tom McGoff, Community Medical Center, Scottsdale, AZ, 1988 May. Format: Cassette (Box VF32)
    - WBBM-CBS. Format: Cassette. TRT: 12:30 (Box VF32)
    - Wind Radio, Chicago. Format: Cassette. TRT: 22:30 (Box VF32)
    - Frank Hardie Advertising; Gannett Outdoor: Try to Forget Us; IOA Mixed Media Marriages II complete; IOA Mixed Media Marriages II live. Format: DVD (Box VF33)
    - A.D.; Gannett Outdoor: Hollywood Cuts; Inside Champion v.4, pt.3; 1985/1986 OBIE Awards. Format: DVD (Box VF33)
    - David Maxwell/PETA ad; Mediacom Inc. David Bernstein lecture; OAAA/TAB Our System; Outdoor Systems 1999 Sales Meeting. Format: DVD (Box VF33)
    - IOA: 1987 OBIE Awards; Metromedia: Faces that Stand Out in a Crowd; Power of Lintas; TAB Perspectives. Format: DVD (Box VF33)
    - Nagele: The New Messenger. Format: DVD (Box VF33)
    - OAAA: Outdoor America. Format: DVD (Box VF33)
    - Roadsters, Rumbleseats & Country Drives. Format: DVD (Box VF33)
    - Signs and Rhymes of Burma-Shave. Format: DVD (Box VF33)
    - Treasure Island. Format: DVD (Box VF33)
    - Inside Outdoor Advertising; The Discrimination Complaint Process. Format: DVD (Box VF33)
    - So Your Plant is Getting Audited; Highway Dollars and Sense. Format: DVD (Box VF33)
    - Highways to Confusion; Federal Money and State Roads; Puzzling Billboard; Chicago Paint Experiment. Format: DVD (Box VF33)
    - CBS News on the Road; In More Ways Than One; Outdoors the New Messenger. Format: DVD (Box VF33)
    - Women's Crusade for Seat Belts; Think Big; Notre Dame Driving Simulator; Noisy Landscapes; New York Paint Experiment. Format: DVD (Box VF33)
    - 100 Years of Outdoor; Birth of a Notion; Case of the Roving Eyes; Foster and Kleiser. Format: DVD (Box VF33)
    - Barrett Outdoor Communications. News feature on sign painter Russell Rainbolt, 2002.. Format: DVD (Box VF33)
    - Sign (Firm) Co.--Billboard Production in Portugal, from Francisco Mesquita, 2002. Format: DVD (Box VF33)
    - YESCO Archive. Young Electric Sign Company, Salt Lake City, Utah (served Utah, Nevada area). Format: DVD (Box VF33)
    - HCD-OAAA-AR1--Promos for OAAA. Format: CD (Box VF33)
    - HCD-OAAA-AR4--F&K #1. Format: CD (Box VF33)
    - HCD-OAAA-AR5--Foster & Kleiser Master Presentation. Format: CD (Box VF33)
    - HCD-OAAA-AR7--F&K Chicago narration. Format: CD (Box VF33)
    - HCD-OAAA-AR8--Traffic reel 1. Format: CD (Box VF33)
    - HCD-OAAA-AR9--Traffic reel 2. Format: CD (Box VF33)
    - HCD-OAAA-PD1--OAAA, Outdoor Advertising's '62 New Car Promotion. Format: CD (Box VF33)
    - HCD-OAAA-PD2--Carling Brewing Company radio spots. Format: CD (Box VF33)
    - HCD-OAAA-PD3--OAAA public service announcements. Format: CD (Box VF33)
    - HCD-OAAA-PD4--OAI, Wonderful World of Signs RSMC-1424/1425. Format: CD (Box VF33)
    - HCD-OAAA-PD5--General Foods, Getting More Customers. Format: CD (Box VF33)
    - HCD-OAAA-PD6--When America's Front Door Opens. Format: CD (Box VF33)
    - HCD-OAAA-PD7--Outdoor--Vital Medium in Today's Grocery Field. Format: CD (Box VF33)
    - HCD-OAAA-PD8--Your Outdoor Neighbor, Bell/Automatic 30-50 versions. Format: CD (Box VF33)
    - HCD-OAAA-PD9--Your Outdoor Neighbor, revised. Format: CD (Box VF33)
- OVERSIZE MATERIALS SERIES, 1885-1979
  Note: Oversize materials are housed in three types of containers: Oversize Boxes, Large Oversize Boxes, and Oversize Folders.
  - Oversize Boxes (Box VF33)
  - Administration-Officers Series
    - Anniversary Issue (Box OV1)
      - OAAA News, 1941 (Box OV1)
    - Holan, Walter
      - General Outdoor Advertising Company: Rates and Allotments, 1956-1962 (Box OV1)
    - Officers
      - Eastern District, 1904 (Box OV1)
  - Budget/Finance Series
    - Budget & Cost Accounting, 1922-1936 (Box OV1)
    - Cost Accounting, 1929-1941 (Box OV1)
    - Cost Accounting Research, 1925-1928 (Box OV1)
    - Cost Finding, 1934-1938 (Box OV1)
    - Dues, 1928-1957 (Box OV1)
    - Financial Reports, 1935-1954 (Box OV1)
    - Miscellaneous, 1907-1915 (Box OV1)
      [Letters, Bills, Invoices, Etc.]
    - Notre Dame Accounting Study, 1944-1948 (Box OV1)
    - Oversized Exhibits of H.E. Fisk, 1918-1947 (Box OV1)
      [Includes income schedule; expenses]
    - Painted Display--Cost Analysis, 1936-1949 (Box OV1)
  - Campaign Case Studies Series
    - Automotive
      - Chevrolet, 1961-1963 (Box OV1)
      - Miscellaneous, 1921-1926, 2 folders (Box OV1)
        [Contains use copies and original scrapbook. General Outdoor Advertising Company, Outdoor Advertising Plan]
      - Vista Wax (Simoniz), ca. 1959 (Box OV1)
    - Household
      - Appliances -Maytag, ca. 1926, 2 folders (Box OV1)
        [General OutdoorAdvertising Company, Outdoor Advertising Plan]
      - Furnishings, ca. 1924, 2 folders (Box OV1)
        [General Outdoor Advertising Company, Outdoor Advertising Plan]
    - Candy (Box OV2)
      - O Henry ( Williamson Candy Company), 1921-1926, 2 folders (Box OV2)
    - Cigarette/Tobacco
      - Cigarette/Tobacco, 1953-1963 (Box OV2)
        [An OAI-Philip Morris poster was relocated to Oversize Folder no. 17]
    - Food -Dairy
      - Ice Cream, 1921-1926 (Box OV2)
    - Real Estate
      - FHA Poster Program-- The Small House Market, 1940 (Box OV2)
  - History Series (Box OV3)
    - Car Cards
      - Amoco, ca. 1960, 2 folders (Box OV3)
      - Large historical photographs, undated (Box OV3)
        [Includes ROAD Database items AAA-0090, AAA0100, AAA4778, AAA4780, AAA4789, AAA5375, AAA7572]
      - Majestic Electric Radio, undated (Box OV3)
    - Magazine Clippings on History of Advertising, 1960s-1970s (Box OV3)
    - Poster Advertising Association
      - Rules and Regulations, 1918 (Box OV3)
  - International Series
    - Canada-Agencies
      - Urban Outdoors, 1980 (Box OV3)
    - China -Hong Kong
      - Advertising and Publicity Bureau, undated (Box OV3)
        [Facade Sketch]
  - Issues and Activities Series
    - Building Maintenance and Headquarters
      - Headquarters Task Committee, 1956-1965 (Box OV3)
      - OAAA-Headquarters- Chicago (selling of OAAA property), 1959 (Box OV3)
    - Organization
      - Merger-10A Correspondence and Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box OV3)
      - OAAA Organization Set-up, Titles, Responsibilities, 1931-1952, 2 folders (Box OV3)
    - Press Clippings and Reprints
      - 1910-1939, 1970-1991, 3 folders (Box OV3)
      - Washington Outdoor Advertising Control, ca. 1961, 2 folders (Box OV3)
        [Contains use copies and original scrapbook]
    - Press, Trade Publications (Box OV4)
      - Trade Publications Print Media: Circa 1963 (Box OV4)
    - Public Service Associations
      - American Heritage Foundation preface by Department of Justice, 1946-1949 (Box OV4)
      - Consumers Movement committee on Consumer Relations in Advertising, 1940-1950 (Box OV4)
      - Freedom Foundation Valley Forge, [ca. 1951] (Box OV4)
        [Note: A Poster was removed and placed in the Oversize Folder no. 22]
    - Public Service Campaigns
      - Iran Hostage Crisis, 1980, 2 folders (Box OV4)
      - Literacy Program (photos of Barbara Bush), 1980s, 2 folders (Box OV4)
    - Public Service-General
      - Public Service Reports and Correspondence, 1940-1959 (Box OV4)
      - Recapitulation of Public Policy, Highways, Inventories, 1947 (Box OV4)
    - Sales Planning
      - Planning, Miscellaneous, 1930-1959 (Box OV4)
      - Sales Statistics-Sale of the Top 100 Outdoor Advertisers, 1957-1962 (Box OV4)
    - Sales Presentations
      - Bank Appeal, undated, 8 folders (Box OV4)
      - Coal Promotion Presentation, undated [Stand-up chart book] (Box OV5)
      - See Power = Sales Power, ca. 1956, 8 folders (Box OV5)
    - Sales Promotion
      - Promotion-Local Interest, 1936-1942 (Box OV5)
    - Wartime--WWII (Box OV6)
      - OAAA News--Wartime Souvenir Edition, 1945 (Box OV6)
      - Press Clipping: Army Times, 1944 (Box OV6)
      - Record of War Activities, 1942-1945 (Box OV6)
      - Record of War Activities of the Outdoor Advertising Industry World War II, 1945 Nov. (Box OV6)
      - Report of the Director of War Activities, 1945, 4 folders (Box OV6)
      - Report to the President, 1945, 3 folders (Box OV6)
  - Local Markets Series (Box OV7)
    - California-- Los Angeles-- F & K Metroplex Coverage Plan, 1970s (Box OV7)
    - California--Northern -- F & K Metroplex Coverage Plan, 1970s (Box OV7)
    - Illinois-- Chicago - F & K Metroplex Coverage Plan, 1970s (Box OV7)
    - Indiana: A Survey of Highway Traffic Flow, Market Data and Poster Advertising Facilities, 1932 (Box OV7)
    - Multiple Site Studies
      - A Survey of Shopping Hours and Night Openings in 140 Media Records Cities, 1962 (Box OV7)
    - New York
      - Market Data, Traffic Circulation, Outdoor Advertising, 1933 (Box OV7)
        [Cover Marked: No. 50 assigned to H.E. Fisk, Outdoor Advertising Association of America, Chicago, Illinois. NOTE: Oversized materials placed in Oversize Folder no. 21]
      - New York State Market, 1933 (Box OV7)
        [Published by the Outdoor Advertising Association of New York]
      - New York City, F & K Metroplex Coverage Plan, 1970s (Box OV7)
      - New York City -Times Square Displays Scrapbook, ca. 1935 [Access copies] (Box OV7)
        [Produced by General Outdoor Advertising Company; collection of historic electrical spectaculars dating from ca. 1914]
      - New York City -Times Square Displays Scrapbook, ca. 1935 [Originals], 3 folders (Box OV7)
      - New York City -Brooklyn, Survey of 24-Sheet Poster Display, 1931, 10 folders (Box OV8)
    - Ohio-- F & K Metroplex Coverage Plan, 1970s (Box OV8)
    - Pacific Northwest - F & K Metroplex Coverage Plan, 1970s (Box OV8)
  - Meetings Series (Box OV9)
    - Annual
      - Call for the 36th Annual Convention of the Poster Advertising Association, 1926 (Box OV9)
      - OAAA Convention, 1985 (Box OV9)
    - Board of Directors
      - Chicago, Ill., 1931 Jan. 20-21 (Box OV9)
      - French Lick, Ind., 1947 May 14-16 (Box OV9)
      - Chicago, Ill., 1959 June 9 (Box OV9)
    - Historic Convention Coverage, 1890-1940 (Box OV9)
    - Institute of Outdoor Advertising
      - Board of Governor's Meeting Atlanta, Georgia, 1976 April 13 (Box OV9)
    - Poster Advertising Association
      - Invitation to Convention, St. Louis, Mo., 1920 (Box OV9)
    - Officers and Directors-Material Sent, 1930-1947 (Box OV9)
  - Membership Series
    - Records
      - OAAA Membership Records, 1902-1950, Folders 1-6 of 14 (Box OV9)
      - OAAA Membership Records, 1902-1950, Folders 7-14 of 14 (Box OV10)
  - Organization -Committees Series (Box OV11)
    - Poster Standards
      - Panel Conversion Project, 1929 (Box OV11)
  - Organization -Departments and Divisions Series
    - Poster Plant Division
      - Color: Spectrophotometer Recordings, 1950 (Box OV11)
      - Showings, 1929-1949 (Box OV11)
    - Promotions Department
      - Miscellaneous, 1939-1956 (Box OV11)
    - Public Policy Department
      - Campaign- The Jordans, 1952 (Box OV11)
    - Public Relations Department
      - Bicentennial Exhibit, 1976 (Box OV11)
        [Oversize materials also located in Oversize Folder no. 22]
    - Publications and Promotions Division
      - Outdoor Advertising, Reprint of Chapter 6 of Advertising and Its Mechanical Production, 1948 (Box OV11)
  - Outdoor Advertising Companies Series
    - Criterion, undated (Box OV11)
    - Cusack, see Thomas Cusack (Box OV11)
    - Donnelly Outdoor Advertising-sales and promotional material, 1977 (Box OV11)
    - Foster & Kleiser [Dinner for George Kleiser, 1933- New York] (Box OV11)
    - Foster & Kleiser (Box OV11)
      [ National Guard Award, 1949]
    - Foster & Kleiser (Box OV11)
      [Portrait Drawing, undated (left to right: Thomas H.R. Varney (owner of Outdoor Plants in Los Angeles and Oakland, California; predecessor to Foster-Kleiser Ownership), George Kleiser, and Walter Foster)]
    - Gannett Outdoor Network
      - Guide to Out of Home, 1962 (Box OV11)
      - Outdoor Network USA, 1985 (Box OV11)
    - Miscellaneous Companies, 1946-1971 (Box OV11)
      [Removed from Columbus Outdoor files]
    - O'Mealia Advertising Public Service- Vietnam Scrapbook, 1965 (Box OV11)
    - Thomas Cusack Advertising-sales and promotional material, [ca. 1932?] (Box OV11)
    - United Advertising - sales and promotional material, undated (Box OV11)
      [Includes materials from Hansen Advertising Companies]
  - Physical Structure Series (Box OV12)
    - Aluminum and Steel
      - Metal Cleaner, 1950-1951 (Box OV12)
      - Stainless Steel Care and Maintenance, 1950-1951 (Box OV12)
    - Artwork, Lithograph, and Printing
      - Printing Procedure Inquiry, 1946-1957 (Box OV12)
    - Color and Paint
      - Lettering Color Schemes, [1950s] (Box OV12)
    - General Construction
      - Akron clinic, 1949 (Box OV12)
      - Loewy and Associates, 1949 (Box OV12)
      - Loewy Panel, Drawings, 1949 (Box OV12)
      - Poster Panel Drawings and Illumination Graph, 1947-1957 (Box OV12)
      - Various Drawings, 1955 and undated (Box OV12)
    - Patents Folder
      - Drawing, 1885 (Box OV12)
    - Poles and Anchorage
      - Cantilever Nomographic Chart-Embedment of Posts with Overturning Loads, 1947 (Box OV12)
    - Posters
      - Rain Lap Posters Drawing, 1941-1956 (Box OV12)
    - Posting
      - Posting Methods-Short Handle Posting, 1935-1949 (Box OV12)
      - Plywood Paste Tanks, Drawings, 1952-1953 and undated (Box OV12)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Plastics, Drawings, 1944-1953 (Box OV12)
  - Publications Series
    - Marketing
      - A Tour Through an Outdoor Advertising Plant, undated (Box OV12)
    - OAA Newsletter, 1938 Jan. (Box OV12)
  - Regulation Series
    - Interest Group--American Automobile Association News Review, 1947-1948 (Box OV12)
  - Research Series
    - Coverage
      - Markets-Small Town, 1932-1960 (Box OV12)
      - Reports-Report of the Service Committee, 1938 (Box OV12)
        [Supplement to: Procedure for Delivery of Equalized Coverage Showings, 1938 Nov. 11]
      - Showings, 1938-1940 (Box OV12)
    - Outdoor Advertising Research Institute (OARI)
      - Outdoor Copy and Readership Information, 1955-1956 (Box OV12)
  - State Associations - Kansas
    - Outdoor Advertising Association of Kansas, 1932 (Box OV12)
      [Certificate of Charter from OAAA]
  - TAB Series
    - TAB Audit Bureau, 1962 (Box OV12)
  - Large Oversize Boxes (Box OV12)
  - Budget/Finance Series (Box OV13)
    - Budget & Cost Accounting, 1922-1936 (Box OV13)
    - Cost Accounting, 1929-1941 (Box OV13)
    - Costfinder--Reprints, undated (Box OV13)
    - Painted Display--Cost Analysis, 1936-1949 (Box OV13)
    - Taxes, 1933-1937 (Box OV13)
  - Campaign Case Studies Series
    - Christmas
      - Christmas Accounts, 1954-1955 (Box OV13)
    - Radio/Televison
      - Radio, [1932-1957] (Box OV13)
  - History Series
    - Wartime -WWII
      - Wartime Paper Salvage including Scrapings Baler Drawing, 1942 and undated (Box OV13)
  - Issues and Activities Series
    - Associations
      - War Advertising Council No. 2 [ 1944-1945] (Box OV13)
    - Building Maintenance and Headquarters
      - Facilities Maintenance of Headquarters, 1946-1958 (Box OV13)
    - Committees
      - War Activities Organization and Responsibilities Chart; War Activities Committee, 1943 (Box OV13)
    - Organization
      - OAAA Organization Set-up, Titles, Responsibilities, 1931-1952, 2 folders (Box OV13)
      - Reorganization Plan, 1931 (Box OV13)
    - Press Clippings and Reprints
      - Clippings and Reprints, 1930-1939 (Box OV13)
      - Clippings, 1956-1959 (Box OV13)
    - Public Service Campaigns
      - Family Theater Correspondence, 1948-1955 (Box OV13)
      - Fight Back Posting Campaign, Iran Hostage Crisis, 1980 (Box OV13)
    - Reports and Publications (Box OV13)
      - TAB Study of Postwar Activities, 1944 Dec. (Box OV13)
  - Local Markets Series (Box OV13)
    - Pennsylvania: Market and Outdoor Advertising Circulation, 1933, 10 folders (Box OV13)
      [NOTE: 3 items removed to Oversize Folder 23 (see listing below); 2 items placed in Local Markets Series, box LM6]
      Folder 1: Miscellaneous
      Folder 2: Traffic flow maps: Aliquippa - Butler
      Folder 3: Traffic flow maps: Carbondale - Corry
      Folder 4: Traffic flow maps: Darby - Franklin
      Folder 5: Traffic flow maps: Gettysburg - Johnstown
      Folder 6: Traffic flow maps: Lancaster - Mt. Carmel
      Folder 7: Traffic flow maps: Nanticoke - Punxatawny
      Folder 8: Traffic flow maps: Reading - Sunbury
      Folder 9: Traffic flow maps: Tamaqua - York
      Folder 10: Traffic flow maps of the principal retail trading centers in Southern New Jersey
  - Membership Series (Box OV14)
    - Dues
      - Minimum Plant Requirements of Town Membership and Recommended Plant Capacity, 1927-1948 (Box OV14)
  - Organization -Committees Series
    - Defense Mobilization Committee
      - Manpower and Plant Facilities Survey, 1951 (Box OV14)
    - Poster Standard Committee
      - 205 [?] Panel Conversion Project, 1929 (Box OV14)
    - Public Policy
      - Clean-up/Paint-up/Fix-up Programs, 1953 (Box OV14)
  - Organization Departments and Divisions Series
    - Poster Plant Development Division
      - Karl Ghaster Collection, 1948-1955 (Box OV14)
      - Rain-Lap Poster, Correspondence, etc. 1930-1947 (Box OV14)
    - Research and Engineering Division
      - Illumination Project-Calculations, 1957 and undated (Box OV14)
      - Illumination Project-Manufacturers Test Data, 1938 and undated (reflector, lighting plan, foot candles, energy output, fluorescent and filament) (Box OV14)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Papers, 1927-1981 (Oversize flyers-Lettering Color Schemes; Lettering Good and Bad; poster-home laundry equipment) (Box OV14)
  - Outdoor Advertising Companies Series
    - Gumpentz/Bentley/Fried, 1982 (Box OV14)
  - Physical Structure Series
    - Aluminum and Steel
      - Foster and Kleiser Loewy Poster Panel Illumination Details, Blueprint, 1949 (Box OV14)
    - General Construction (Box OV14)
      - Drawings and Blueprints, 1950-1952 (Box OV14)
    - Miscellaneous (Box OV14)
      - Panel Construction and Anchorage, 1946-1947 (Box OV14)
        [Includes drawings and blueprints from similarly labeled file in regular size part of series. See this file for context]
      - Standard and Poster Panels, 1944-1948 (Box OV14)
    - Poles and Anchorage
      - Miscellaneous, 1946-1947 (Box OV14)
      - Soil Studies, 1947-1950 (Box OV14)
    - Posters
      - Coca-Cola Flagging Posters, undated (Box OV14)
      - Poster Reclamation Drawings, 1942 (Box OV14)
      - Priorities-Paper, Drawings, 1941-1942 (Box OV14)
      - Survey of Bulletin Standards, undated (Box OV14)
  - Regulation Series
    - Topics
      - Billboard Controversy-Proposed Poster, Supporting A Beautiful America, 1965 (Box OV14)
  - Trade Organizations Series
    - British Poster Advertising Association (BPAA)
      - London Times Article on 100 Years of British Posters ( 1861-1961), 1961 (Box OV14)
    - Outdoor Advertising, Inc. (OAI)
      - Campaigns-Proof Sheets and Memos, 1958 (Box OV14)
      - OAI Promotional Materials, undated (Box OV14)
    - Promotional
      - Promotional Advertising, 1955-1956 (Box OV14)
      - Promotional materials and correspondence, 1956 (Box OV14)
  - Campaign Case Studies (Box OV15)
    - Scrapbook, Colgate -Palmolive - Peet, ca. 1941 (Box OV15)
      [Use copies and original. Bound original is fragile, contains loose items.]
  - Trade Organizations (Box OV16)
    - Outdoor Advertising, Inc., Publication, 1938 (Box OV16)
      [ Urban markets and Retail Sales: A New Approach to Market Evaluation by John Brennan]
  - Full-Sized Poster Sheets, 1962-1976 and undated
    Folded sheets for 5, 6, 8, 10, 12, 24 and 30-sheet posters and billboards. Many comprise incomplete sets. Where known, the artist is noted.
    - Knickerbocker Beer 8-sheet, For The Record We Pay By Check (Howard Scott) 8-sheet 1962, Graphics in America 5-sheet (Antonakos), Pepsi (girl)--Pepsi's got a Lot to Give 30-sheet, I Bank for Security (Howard Scott) 8-sheet 1962 (Box OV17)
    - Come Home to Ford 30-sheet, Knickerbocker Beer (Howard Scott) 8-sheet incomplete, Seagram's 10-sheet, Bull durham 24-sheet incomplete, If Attacks Come 24-sheet incomplete (Box OV18)
    - National Association for Mental Health 24-sheet, Loan Your Worries Away (Howard Scott) 8-sheet incomplete, For the Record (Howard Scott) 6-sheet incomplete, I Bank (Howard Scott) 8-sheet incomplete, Smiling Woman (Howard Scott) 8-sheet incomplete, Maxwell Thanks to You 100 Years 8-sheet (Box OV19)
    - Kid's Face incomplete, Swan Soap (Howard Scott) 24-sheet incomplete, Schlitz blonde female tennis player 24-sheet, Studebaker Golden Hawk 12-sheet, Those Inward Qualities That Make Friends and Hold Them, Camel--Where Real Cigarette Pleasure Begins (Box OV20)
    - If You Smoke for Pleasure Get to Know Camels, Clean Cut Merit Camels, Give Me a Camel, Camel Green Hat 24-sheet, Gulf Oil Fish 12-sheet, Esso Standard--Hold Back Your Speed 24-sheet (Box OV21)
    - OAAA U.S. Bicentennial 30-sheet: Design 1--Next 200; Design 2--200 Years Old (Box OV22)
    - Benson & Hedges Clown 12-sheet, Pacific Outdoor--Fight Back Drive 55 30-sheet, Camel--Compare the Tobacco 24-sheet, Bull Durham 24-sheet, Camel #46 30-sheet, Camel #106--Red Dress 24-sheet (Box OV23)
    - OAAA U.S. Bicentennial 30-sheet: Design 2--200 Years Old; Happy Birthday America (Box OV24)
    - Camel#13: I'd Walk a Mile; Camel#3: Camels Are the Choice of Those Who Know the Facts about Cigarettes; Camel#20: The Choice of the Experienced Smoker; Camel#17: Worthy; Camel#18: Goodbye to All the Others (Box OV25)